{
    "id": "b254f1e901934283b773cc69a6103191",
    "title": "Linking Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He suffered many setbacks, …………………………. he persisted.",
            "description": "But is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "despite",
                "however"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0fbea1d95c1946a8b49242ecbca64af7"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. his illness, he looked cheerful.",
            "description": "Despite is a preposition. It is followed by a noun or ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Although",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2b01661900ed4c2793c152cfa19735b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "They fought hard, ……………………… they were defeated.",
            "description": "However is not a conjunction. It cannot connect two clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "however",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "23252bc36e4b42f793f14ffd34cec9ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "She works hard …………………………., she does not earn much.",
            "description": "However is a transitional adverb. It does not connect two clauses. However follows a full stop or semicolon. ",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "however",
                "though"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "729a1dc2fe30463aa5c9716c883646a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The party was fun …………………………, I went home early.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "despite",
                "but",
                "though",
                "however"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "d3d7f0916a434135bc2f747ebc0a18e6"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… trying hard, he could not move the table.",
            "description": "Despite is followed by a noun or ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Though",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fdb99ad21cdb40e686a80c0403acbac6"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. I missed the bus, I still managed to reach on time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "However",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "26dfbc51f249480eb5804338a50d3b65"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. their best efforts, they could not save her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "However",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "df5c6cfb68a94745aa9fb4137b5db761"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctors tried hard ……………………………, they could not save her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "however",
                "though",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3062b61b06aa47a28c6e8fd7321a03c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. suffering grievous injuries, he is hopeful of making a complete recovery.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Though",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "01e6f34c86da4fbcbcfff2208704baa8"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. she was the most deserving student, she did not get admission.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "However",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "14d579b163d64cb6b037475e1b825ce1"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. hard you may try, you will not succeed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "However",
                "Though",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6fd6f22eda1b4e7281ea31b0e974667b"
        }
    ]
}